A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20 FA292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Files, 1920-1993; 2; 242 Box(es)
  - Deas, Henry Thomas - 1925 - England - Literature, 1925-1975 (Box 50, Folder 416)
  - Deasey, Randal Hugh - 1954 - Australia - Public Administration, 1954-1987 (Box 51, Folder 417)
  - DeBoom, Henri Pieter Albert - 1953 - South Africa - Biological Science, 1953-1979 (Box 51, Folder 418)
  - DeFay-Flausch, Marianne - 1977 - Belgium - Literature, 1977-1987 (Box 51, Folder 419)
  - DeGraeve, Marie Christine - 1977 - Belgium - Archaeology, 1976-1986 (Box 51, Folder 420)
  - Delafons, John - 1959 - England - Architecture, 1958-1988 (Box 51, Folder 421)
  - DeLisle, Edwin William - 1951 - New Zealand - Telecommunications, 1951-1979 (Box 51, Folder 422)
  - DeMarco, Sergio - 1959 - Italy - American Studies, 1958-1980 (Box 51, Folder 423)
  - Denley, Elizabeth - 1981 - Australia - Oceanography, 1980-1986 (Box 51, Folder 424)
  - Derrington, Patrice Anne - 1979 - Australia - Architecture, 1978-1986 (Box 51, Folder 425)
  - Deschamps, Robert - 1968 - Belgium - Economics, 1967-1982 (Box 52, Folder 426)
  - Deswaan, Abraham - 1966 - Amsterdam - Political Science, 1966-1975 (Box 52, Folder 427)
  - Deuchar, Margaret - 1974 - England - Linguistics, 1973-1988 (Box 52, Folder 428)
  - Deverall, Brian James - 1960 - England - Pathology, 1959-1975 (Box 52, Folder 429)
  - Devlin, Stuart - 1960 - Australia - Sculpture, 1959-1985 (Box 52, Folder 430)
  - Dewet, Jacobus Stephanus - 1938 - England - Mathematics, 1938-1984 (Box 52, Folder 431)
  - Diamond, Michael - 1987 - England - Theatre Management, 1986-1990 (Box 52, Folder 432)
  - Dick, Marcus - 1951 - England - Mathematics, 1950-1975 (Box 52, Folder 433)
  - Dickinson, James Chris Meade - 1985 - England - International Relations, 1984-1990 (Box 53, Folder 434)
  - DiMaria, Eugenio - 1973 - Italy - Journalism, 1971-1984 (Box 53, Folder 435)
  - DiPaola, Luigi - 1966 - Italy - Business Administration, 1965-1984 (Box 53, Folder 436)
  - Dippenaar, Berand Jacobus - 1931 - South Africa - Pathology, 1931-1981 (Box 53, Folder 437)
  - Dixon, David - 1953 - England - Law, 1952-1979 (Box 53, Folder 438)
  - Dobbs, Henry Adrian Conway - 1950 - England - Sociology, 1946-1970 (Box 53, Folder 439)
  - Dobson, Colin - 1970 - Australia - Parasitology, 1969-1985 (Box 53, Folder 440)
  - Dobson, Mary Janet - 1978 - England - Demography, 1977-1987 (Box 53, Folder 441)
  - Dodwell, David William - 1932 - England - Economics, 1932-1980 (Box 54, Folder 442)
  - Doherty, Richard Ralph - 1983 - Australia - Medicine, 1982-1986 (Box 54, Folder 443)
  - Donald, Bruce George - 1971 - Australia - Law, 1971-1986 (Box 54, Folder 444)
  - Donaldson, Anthony Christopher - 1966 - England - Painting, 1966-1990 (Box 54, Folder 445)
  - Donati, Ada - 1964 - Italy - Poetry, 1964-1971 (Box 54, Folder 446)
  - Doone, Peter Eric Charles - 1984 - New Zealand - Law, 1984-1987 (Box 54, Folder 447)
  - Doornbos, Martin - 1962 - Netherlands - Political Science, 1957-1984 (Box 54, Folder 448)
  - Dorel, Martine - 1976 - France - Linguistics, 1975-1986 (Box 54, Folder 449)
  - Dorflinger, Hans - 1966 - Germany - Painting, 1965-1985 (Box 54, Folder 450)
  - Douglas, Donald - 1937 - England - Medicine, 1937-1985 (Box 55, Folder 451)
  - Doumic, Claude - 1961 - France - Business Administration, 1960-1976 (Box 55, Folder 452)
  - Doumic, Claude - 1961 - France - Business Administration, 1960-1976 (Box 55, Folder 453)
  - Dove, John - 1960 - England - Chemistry, 1969-1975 (Box 55, Folder 454)
  - Dow, Julian Alexander Thomas - 1981 - England - Zoology, 1980-1985 (Box 55, Folder 455)
  - Downes, John Antony - 1937 - England - Entomology, 1937-1975 (Box 55, Folder 456)
  - Downs, Ronald Geoffrey - 1954 - Australia - Agriculture, Fisheries and Wildlife, Forestry, 1954-1985 (Box 55, Folder 457)
  - Drachkovitch, Milorad - 1955 - Belgium - Political Science, 1954-1975 (Box 56, Folder 458)
  - Drake, Eric - 1927 - England - Drama, 1927-1975 (Box 56, Folder 459)
  - Drew, Kathleen Mary - 1925 - England - Botany, 1925-1963 (Box 56, Folder 460)
  - Drought, Arthur Benjamin - 1946 - England - Architecture, 1946-1975 (Box 56, Folder 461)
  - Drummond, Irwin John - 1975 - Ireland - Business Administration, 1975-1984 (Box 56, Folder 462)
  - Dubsky, Mario - 1969 - England - Painting, 1968-1985 (Box 56, Folder 463)
  - Duchatelet-Moore, Martine - 1973 - Belgium - Economics, 1972-1980 (Box 57, Folder 464)
  - Duck, Jonathan Matthew - 1985 - England - Business Administration, 1984-1987 (Box 57, Folder 465)
  - Dufau, Olivier Pierre - 1970 - France - Architecture, 1970-1986 (Box 57, Folder 466)
  - Duff, Iain Spencer - 1972 - England - Mathematics, 1971-1975 (Box 57, Folder 467)
  - Duffield, John - 1931 - England - Zoology, 1931-1975 (Box 57, Folder 468)
  - Duffill, David - 1975 - England - Business Administration, 1974-1988 (Box 57, Folder 469)
  - Duffy, Francis - 1967 - England - Architecture, 1967-1989 (Box 58, Folder 470)
  - Duffy, Simon - 1976 - England - Business Administration, 1973-1987 (Box 58, Folder 471)
  - Duke-Evans, Jonathan Blase - 1989 - England - Public Administration, 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 472)
  - Dummett, Michael Anthony - 1955 - England - Mathematics, 1954-1985 (Box 58, Folder 473)
  - Dunbar, Norman - 1947 - England - Law, 1947-1976 (Box 58, Folder 474)
  - Duncan, Walter - 1930 - Australia - Sociology, 1930-1976 (Box 58, Folder 475)
  - Dunham, Kingsley - 1932 - England - Geology, 1932-1988 (Box 58, Folder 476)
  - Dunn, John - 1964 - England - History, 1963-1984 (Box 59, Folder 477)
  - Dunsby, Jonathan - 1976 - England - Music, 1976-1990 (Box 59, Folder 478)
  - Dunsire, Andrew - 1951 - England - Public Administration, 1951-1985 (Box 59, Folder 479)
  - Dupre, John - 1978 - England - Philosophy, 1977-1984 (Box 59, Folder 480)
  - Durie, Mark John - 1984 - Australia - Linguistics, 1984-1987 (Box 59, Folder 481)
  - Dutoit, Rene Michel - 1937 - England - Parasitology, 1935-1987 (Box 59, Folder 482)
  - Dwyer, Terence Michael - 1976 - Australia - Economics, 1975-1986 (Box 59, Folder 483)
  - Dykes, John Christopher - 1936 - England - Aeronautical Engineering, 1936-1981 (Box 59, Folder 484)
  - Dykes, Paul - 1931 - England - Electrical Engineering, 1931-1990 (Box 59, Folder 485)
  - Dyson, Freeman John - 1947 - England - Physics, 1947-1984 (Box 59, Folder 486)
  - Easterbrook, Philippa Jane - 1987 - England - Medicine, 1986-1990 (Box 60, Folder 487)
  - Eccles, Dennis - 1964 - England - Engineering, 1963-1975 (Box 60, Folder 488)
  - Edgecombe, Ralph - 1931 - England - Irrigation, 1931-1976 (Box 60, Folder 489)
  - Edwards, Andrew John Cumming - 1971 - England - Economics, 1970-1984 (Box 60, Folder 490)
  - Edwards, Anthony Martin - 1974 - Australia - Biochemistry, 1973-1977 (Box 60, Folder 491)
  - Edwards, Eric Thomas Allen - 1937 - Australia - Agriculture, 1936-1982 (Box 60, Folder 492)
  - Edwards, Peter - 1975 - Australia - History, 1974-1987 (Box 60, Folder 493)
  - Edwards, Philip Walter - 1954 - England - English Literature, 1953-1986 (Box 60, Folder 494)
  - Eisenbach, Claus Dieter - 1974 - Germany - Chemistry, 1973-1980 (Box 60, Folder 495)
  - Elam, Keir - 1974 - England - Linguistics, 1973-1981 (Box 61, Folder 496)
  - Elderfield, John - 1970 - England - Art History, 1969-1985 (Box 61, Folder 497)
  - Eley, Peter David Richard - 1966 - England - Architecture, 1966-1990 (Box 61, Folder 498)
  - Elias, Rahael - 1979 - England - Journalism, 1978-1990 (Box 61, Folder 499)
  - Elliott, Royce Edwin Walter - 1968 - New Zealand - Cellular Immunology, 1968-1984 (Box 61, Folder 500)
  - Ellis, Daniel Patrick - 1989 - England - Electrical Engineering, 1989-1991 (Box 61, Folder 501)
  - Elvin, H. Lionel - 1928 - England - English Literature, 1930-1990 (Box 61, Folder 502)
  - Elvin, John - 1962 - England - History, 1962-1985 (Box 61, Folder 503)
  - Emeleus, Harry Julius - 1929 - England - Chemistry, 1929-1987 (Box 61, Folder 504)
  - Emery, Victor - 1959 - England - Physics, 1959-1984 (Box 61, Folder 505)
  - Emmet, Dorothy - 1928 - England - Philosophy, 1928-1987 (Box 62, Folder 506)
  - Empson, John Desmond - 1954 - England - Agricultural Policy, 1953-1989 (Box 62, Folder 507)
  - Emslie, Alfred - 1930 - Scotland - Physics, 1930-1952 (Box 62, Folder 508)
  - Ernotte, Andre - 1970 - Belgium - Theatre, 1969-1984 (Box 62, Folder 509)
  - Esselen, Daniel - 1930 - England - Agriculture, 1930-1950 (Box 62, Folder 510)
  - Evans, Andrew - 1988 - England - Business Administration, 1987-1990 (Box 62, Folder 511)
  - Evans, Harold - 1956 - England - Journalism, 1956-1987 (Box 62, Folder 512)
  - Evans, Hywell - 1957 - England - Industrial Relatinos, 1957-1961 (Box 62, Folder 513)
  - Evans, Lloyd Thomas - 1954 - New Zealand - Plant Physiology, 1954-1981 (Box 63, Folder 514)
  - Evans, Peter David - 1973 - England - Biological Science, 1972-1988 (Box 63, Folder 515)
  - Evans, Philip - 1972 - England - Economics, 1971-1984 (Box 63, Folder 516)
  - Everett, James Edgar - 1961 - Australia - Geophysics, 1960-1987 (Box 63, Folder 517)
  - Fabb, Nigel - 1980 - England - Linguistics, 1976-1987 (Box 63, Folder 518)
  - Fairman, Marion - 1956 - England - Virology, 1955-1987 (Box 63, Folder 519)
  - Falk, Nicholas Phillip Horton - 1967 - England - Public Administration, 1967-1989 (Box 63, Folder 520)
  - Falsone, Gioacchino - 1970 - Italy - Anthropology, 1968-1982 (Box 63, Folder 521)
  - Fane, Charles George - 1968 - England - Economics, 1967-1980 (Box 64, Folder 522)
  - Faris, Samuel Alexander - 1956 - England - Creative Arts, 1955-1990 (Box 64, Folder 523)
  - Farrell, James Gordon - 1966 - England - Literature and Drama, 1965-1985 (Box 64, Folder 524)
  - Farrell, Michael James - 1951 - England - Economics, 1950-1977 (Box 64, Folder 525)
  - Farrell, Terence - 1962 - England - Architecture, 1962-1987 (Box 64, Folder 526)
  - Farrer, Julia - 1974 - England - Print Making, 1973-1990 (Box 64, Folder 527)
  - Farrow, Christopher - 1968 - England - Economics, 1968-1986 (Box 64, Folder 528)
  - Fastborg, Kjell - 1953 - Switzerland - Medical Science, 1953-1959 (Box 64, Folder 529)
  - Faulkner, Gwendoline - 1929 - England - Zoology, 1929-1948 (Box 64, Folder 530)
  - Faull, Richard - 1975 - New Zealand - Medicine and Biomedical Sciences, 1974-1982 (Box 64, Folder 531)
  - Feaver, Benjamin - 1953 - England - Forestry, 1953-1984 (Box 65, Folder 532)
  - Feaver, Benjamin - 1953 - England - Forestry, 1953-1984 (Box 65, Folder 533)
  - Feaver, Benjamin - 1953 - England - Forestry, 1953-1984 (Box 65, Folder 534)
  - Feick, Jurgen - 1975 - Germany - Political Science, 1974-1979 (Box 65, Folder 535)
  - Fells, Peter - 1966 - England - Opthamology, 1966-1990 (Box 65, Folder 536)
  - Ferdinand, Charles - 1973 - England - Russian Studies, 1973-1979 (Box 65, Folder 537)
  - Ferguson, Mary Jean - 1954 - England - Psychology, 1954-1989 (Box 65, Folder 538)
  - Ferrara, Alessandro - 1977 - Italy - Philosophy/Linguistics, 1977-1985 (Box 65, Folder 539)
  - Ferraresi, Franco - 1963 - Italy - Sociology, 1962-1984 (Box 66, Folder 540)
  - Fielding, John Mervyn - 1948 - Australia - Forestry, 1946-1977 (Box 66, Folder 541)
  - Fisher, Henry - 1930 - England - Engienering, 1930-1985 (Box 66, Folder 542)
  - Fisher, Robert - 1926 - England - Economics, 1926-1980 (Box 66, Folder 543)
  - Fitch, Albert Alfred - 1930 - England - Geology, 1930-1988 (Box 66, Folder 544)
  - Fleming, William Launcelot - 1929 - England - Geology, 1929-1977 (Box 66, Folder 545)
  - Flemming, John - 1968 - England - Economics, 1968-1984 (Box 66, Folder 546)
  - Fletcher, Clarence John Molyneux - 1934 - England - Chemistry, 1934-1986 (Box 66, Folder 547)
  - Fletcher, Hugh Alasdair - 1970 - New Zealand - Business Administration, 1969-1985 (Box 66, Folder 548)
  - Flood, Richard - 1936 - England - Economics, 1936-1980 (Box 66, Folder 549)
  - Fluck, Winifried - 1968 - England - American Studies, 1967-1983 (Box 67, Folder 550)
  - Foakes, Reginald - 1955 - England - Literature, 1954-1985 (Box 67, Folder 551)
  - Focken, Charles - 1933 - Australia - Geophysics, 1932-1979 (Box 67, Folder 552)
  - Fokkema, Douwe - 1963 - Netherlands - Chinese Literature, 1962-1975 (Box 67, Folder 553)
  - Folger, Michael - 1978 - England - Public Administration, 1977-1990 (Box 67, Folder 554)
  - Forbes, Vernon - 1929 - South Africa - Geology, 1929-1989 (Box 67, Folder 555)
  - Forde, Cyril Daryll - 1928 - England - Anthropology, 1928-1973 (Box 67, Folder 556)
  - Forman, Francis - 1938 - Australia - Geology, 1938-1985 (Box 67, Folder 557)
  - Forsman, John - 1957 - Finland - Music Composition, 1956-1980 (Box 68, Folder 558)
  - Forster, Howard - 1935 - Australia - Agriculture, 1935-1984 (Box 68, Folder 559)
  - Forster, Shirley - 1965 - England - Literature, 1965-1990 (Box 68, Folder 560)
  - Fouquet, Etienne - 1966 - France - Metallurgy, 1965-1985 (Box 68, Folder 561)
  - Fox, Eustace - 1934 - England - Engienering, 1934-1988 (Box 68, Folder 562)
  - Foxcroft, Edmund John - 1952 - Australia - Economics, 1952-1963 (Box 68, Folder 563)
  - Foxon, David - 1959 - England - Literature and Drama, 1959-1979 (Box 68, Folder 564)
  - Francis, Eleanor - 1935 - England - Geography, 1935-1985 (Box 68, Folder 565)
  - Frangniere, Gabriele Leon - 1966 - Belgium - Political Science, 1965-1986 (Box 68, Folder 566)
  - Frank, Armin - 1965 - Germany - Literature, 1965-1981 (Box 69, Folder 567)
  - Frank, Joachim - 1970 - Germany - Physics, 1969-1975 (Box 69, Folder 568)
  - Frank, Joachim - 1970 - Germany - Physics, 1969-1975 (Box 69, Folder 569)
  - Fredet, Jaques - 1970 - France - Architecture, 1968-1985 (Box 69, Folder 570)
  - Freedman, Peter - 1982 - England - Molecular Genetics, 1981-1987 (Box 69, Folder 571)
  - Freedman, Roger Prester - 1966 - England - Biochemistry, 1965-1969 (Box 69, Folder 572)
  - Freeman, John Fergus - 1980 - New Zealand - Public Administration, 1979-1985 (Box 70, Folder 573)
  - Freeman, John Fergus - 1980 - New Zealand - Public Administration, 1979-1985 (Box 70, Folder 574)
  - Freeman, Philip - 1930 - England - Architecture, 1930-1975 (Box 70, Folder 575)
  - French, Leonard - 1965 - Australia - Painting, 1964-1980 (Box 70, Folder 576)
  - Fry, Anthony - 1961 - England - Painting, 1961-1988 (Box 70, Folder 577)
  - Frey, Henry - 1955 - England - Chemistry, 1955-1988 (Box 70, Folder 578)
  - Fry, Thomas - 1929 - England - Law, 1928-1954 (Box 70, Folder 579)
  - Freyburger, Jacques - 1965 - France - Painting, 1965-1986 (Box 70, Folder 580)
  - Funnell, Brian - 1961 - England - Geology, 1960-1975 (Box 70, Folder 581)
  - Furber, Sarah - 1973 - England - Theology, 1973-1990 (Box 70, Folder 582)
  - Gabites, John - 1948 - New Zealand - Meteorology, 1948-1980 (Box 71, Folder 583)
  - Gabler, Hans Walter - 1968 - Germany - Literature and Drama, 1964-1976 (Box 71, Folder 584)
  - Gabler, Hans Walter - 1968 - Germany - Literature and Drama, 1964-1976 (Box 71, Folder 585)
  - Galbraith, William - 1956 - England - Nuclear Physics, 1956-1975 (Box 71, Folder 586)
  - Galgani, Guiseppe - 1956 - Italy - English and American Literature, 1956-1977 (Box 71, Folder 587)
  - Galione, Antony - 1989 - England - Biological Science, 1988-1993 (Box 71, Folder 588)
  - Galland, Bertil - 1957 - Switzerland - Journalism, 1956-1984 (Box 71, Folder 589)
  - Galletti, Robert - 1937 - England - Economics, 1937-1979 (Box 71, Folder 590)
  - Gallivan, Terence - 1984 - England - Law, 1983-1985 (Box 72, Folder 591)
  - Galloway, Stephen Charles - 1981 - England - Film Studies, 1959-1986 (Box 72, Folder 592)
  - Galvin, Bernard Vincent - 1960 - New Zealand - Economics and Public Policy, 1959-1980 (Box 72, Folder 593)
  - Gamble, Alan - 1972 - England - Law, 1971-1987 (Box 72, Folder 594)
  - Gani, Jacques - 1967 - France - Metallurgy, 1966-1975 (Box 72, Folder 595)
  - Garavaglia, Marcello - 1958 - Italy - Civil Engineering, 1957-1985 (Box 72, Folder 596)
  - Garden, Kathleen - 1985 - New Zealand - Engineering, 1984-1987 (Box 72, Folder 597)
  - Gardiner, Jeremy - 1984 - England - Visual Arts, 1983-1990 (Box 72, Folder 598)
  - Gardner-Medwin, David - 1969 - England - Medicine and Biomedical Science, 1968-1984 (Box 73, Folder 599)
  - Gardner-Medwin, Robert - 1933 - England - Architecture, 1933-1975 (Box 73, Folder 600)
  - Gariban, Georges - 1976 - France - Business Administration, 1976-1986 (Box 73, Folder 601)
  - Garmany, John W. - 1946 - England - Economics, 1946-1988 (Box 73, Folder 602)
  - Garside, Geoffrey - 1968 - England - Computer Science, 1967-1973 (Box 73, Folder 603)
  - Gasciogne, Arthur Bamber - 1958 - England - Modern Theatre, 1957-1990 (Box 73, Folder 604)
  - Gates, Sylvester Govett - 1925 - England - Law, 1925-1972 (Box 73, Folder 605)
  - Gee, Hubert - 1938 - England - Unemployment Relief, 1938-1956 (Box 74, Folder 606)
  - Gelpi, Ettore - 1961 - Italy - Adult Education, 1960-1986 (Box 74, Folder 607)
  - Gemmell, Alan - 1935 - England - Plant Pathology, 1935-1986 (Box 74, Folder 608)
  - Gerlach, Wayne - 1984 - Australia - Biology, 1983-1986 (Box 74, Folder 609)
  - Gero, John Steven - 1973 - Australia - Architecture, 1972-1987 (Box 74, Folder 610)
  - Gevers, Michel - 1969 - Belgium - Electrical Engineering, 1968-1986 (Box 74, Folder 611)
  - Ghesquiere, Henri - 1974 - Belgium - Economics, 1974-1978 (Box 74, Folder 612)
  - Gibbon, Alice - 1929 - England - Labor Economics, 1929-1984 (Box 74, Folder 613)
  - Gibbs, Donald - 1952 - England - Medicine, 1952-1966 (Box 75, Folder 614)
  - Gibbs, James Gordon - 1935 - New Zealand - Plant Pathology, 1933-1980 (Box 75, Folder 615)
  - Gibbs, William - 1951 - Australia - Meteorology, 1951-1983 (Box 75, Folder 616)
  - Gibson, Bryan - 1964 - New Zealand - Criminology, 1964-1981 (Box 75, Folder 617)
  - Gibson, Norman James - 1958 - Ireland - Economics, 1957-1979 (Box 75, Folder 618)
  - Giegel, Hans-Joachim - 1968 - Germany - Psychology, 1967-1973 (Box 75, Folder 619)
  - Gifford, Charles - 1931 - England - Economics, 1931-1975 (Box 75, Folder 620)
  - Gilbert, Francis Sylvest - 1981 - England - Applied Biology, 1980-1986 (Box 75, Folder 621)
  - Gilbert, Richard Simon - 1987 - England - Painting, 1986-1992 (Box 76, Folder 622)
  - Gilbert, Robert Goulston - 1970 - Australia - Chemistry, 1970-1985 (Box 76, Folder 623)
  - Gillespie, Ronald - 1953 - England - Inorganic Chemistry, 1953-1985 (Box 76, Folder 624)
  - Gillies, Hamish Grant - 1968 - England - Orthopedic Surgery, 1967-1971 (Box 76, Folder 625)
  - Ginzburg, Andrea - 1966 - Italy - Economics, 1965-1981 (Box 76, Folder 626)
  - Gittings, John - 1961 - England - Chinese Studies, 1961-1984 (Box 76, Folder 627)
  - Glass, David - 1962 - England - Organic Chemistry, 1961-1985 (Box 76, Folder 628)
  - Glastra Van Loon, Jan Frederik - 1954 - Netherlands - Philosophy and Sociology, 1953-1980 (Box 76, Folder 629)
  - Glastra Van Loon, Jan Frederik - 1954 - Netherlands - Philosophy and Sociology, 1953-1980 (Box 76, Folder 630)
  - Glauert, Richard Holroyd - 1952 - England - Organic Chemistry, 1951-1975 (Box 77, Folder 631)
  - Glover, John - 1949 - England - Biochemistry, 1948-1987 (Box 77, Folder 632)
  - Goguel, Anne Marie - 1952 - France - Sociology, 1952-1982 (Box 77, Folder 633)
  - Goldman, Lawrence - 1979 - England - American History, 1978-1990 (Box 77, Folder 634)
  - Gombrich, Richard - 1961 - England - Sanskrit, 1960-1975 (Box 77, Folder 635)
  - Goodhart, William Howard - 1957 - England - Law, 1956-1989 (Box 77, Folder 636)
  - Goodier, Norman - 1929 - England - Engineering, 1929-1970 (Box 77, Folder 637)
  - Goodwin, Daisey - 1983 - England - Film Studies, 1982-1990 (Box 77, Folder 638)
  - Gordon, Isabella - 1926 - Scotland - Zoology, 1926-1962 (Box 77, Folder 639)
  - Gordon, Pamela Caroline - 1987 - England - Medicine, 1987-1988 (Box 77, Folder 640)
  - Gorgoni, Marcello - 1973 - Italy - Agricultural Economics, 1972-1980 (Box 78, Folder 641)
  - Gosling, David - 1957 - England - Architecture, 1956-1990 (Box 78, Folder 642)
  - Goswami, Usha Claire - 1987 - England - Educational Psychology, 1986-1988 (Box 78, Folder 643)
  - Gotting, Martin - 1966 - Germany - Education, 1965-1981 (Box 78, Folder 644)
  - Goudsblom, Johan - 1965 - Netherlands - Sociology, 1964-1975 (Box 78, Folder 645)
  - Gourlay, David - 1950 - England - Theology, 1950-1988 (Box 78, Folder 646)
  - Goyder, Daniel George - 1962 - England - Law, 1962-1986 (Box 78, Folder 647)
  - Grace, Norman - 1931 - England - Chemistry and Physics, 1931-1980 (Box 79, Folder 648)
  - Grage, Torben Willem - 1953 - Denmark - American Studies and History, 1953-1980 (Box 79, Folder 649)
  - Graham, David - 1927 - Ireland - Engineering and Business Administration, 1926-1978 (Box 79, Folder 650)
  - Graham, Janet - 1956 - Scotland - Plant Nutrition, 1956-1975 (Box 79, Folder 651)
  - Graham, Leslie - 1973 - England - Sociology, 1972-1989 (Box 79, Folder 652)
  - Granger, Clive - 1959 - England - Economics, 1958-1981 (Box 79, Folder 653)
  - Grant, Ronald - 1935 - England - Zoology and Physiology, 1935-1975 (Box 79, Folder 654)
  - Grassini, Franco Alfredo - 1956 - Italy - Economics, 1956-1976 (Box 80, Folder 655)
  - Gray, Harold - 1949 - England - Public Administration, 1949-1988 (Box 80, Folder 656)
  - Gray, John Rodger - 1937 - England - Theology, 1937-1984 (Box 80, Folder 657)
  - Gray, Richard - 1967 - England - American Literature, 1966-1985 (Box 80, Folder 658)
  - Gray, Roger - 1978 - England - Economics, 1977-1990 (Box 80, Folder 659)
  - Green, Anthony - 1967 - England - Painting, 1966-1989 (Box 80, Folder 660)
  - Green, Colin - 1958 - England - Chemistry, 1957-1975 (Box 80, Folder 661)
  - Green, Hilda Annie - 1926 - England - Literature and Drama, 1926-1980 (Box 80, Folder 662)
  - Green, Stephen - 1973 - England - Economics, 1973-1984 (Box 80, Folder 663)
  - Greenman, Jonathan - 1961 - England - Physics, 1960-1975 (Box 81, Folder 664)
  - Greeves, Nicholas - 1985 - England - Organic Chemistry, 1984-1988 (Box 81, Folder 665)
  - Grenville, John - 1958 - Germany - History, 1957-1984 (Box 81, Folder 666)
  - Gresford, Guy Barton - 1956 - Australia - Science Administration, 1956-1986 (Box 81, Folder 667)
  - Gresset, Michael - 1966 - France - American Literature, 1965-1975 (Box 81, Folder 668)
  - Grew, Kenneth - 1931 - England - Physics, 1931-1975 (Box 81, Folder 669)
  - Gridley, Richard - 1961 - England - Business Administration, 1960-1986 (Box 81, Folder 670)
  - Griffin, George - 1974 - England - Muscle Physiology, 1976-1988 (Box 82, Folder 671)
  - Griffiths, Paul - 1980 - England - Buddhist Studies, 1979-1983 (Box 82, Folder 672)
  - Griffiths, Philip - 1955 - Australia - Engineering, 1955-1975 (Box 82, Folder 673)
  - Grime, Geoffrey - 1951 - England - Road Safety, 1951-1979 (Box 82, Folder 674)
  - Grimond, John - 1974 - England - American Studies, 1973-1989 (Box 82, Folder 675)
  - Grimsdale, Sara - 1982 - England - Fine Arts, 1981-1990 (Box 82, Folder 676)
  - Grose, Nancy - 1950 - England - Literature, 1949-1985 (Box 83, Folder 677)
  - Gross, John Jacob - 1958 - England - Literature and Publishing, 1957-1990 (Box 83, Folder 678)
  - Gruenberg, Karl Walter - 1955 - Germany - Mathematics, 1955-1977 (Box 83, Folder 679)
  - Guerin, Bruce - 1971 - Australia - Journalism, 1970-1984 (Box 83, Folder 680)
  - Gugenheim, Victor - 1952 - Germany - Mathematics and Statistics, 1952-1975 (Box 83, Folder 681)
  - Gullvag, Ingemund - 1957 - Norway - Philosophy, 1956-1975 (Box 83, Folder 682)
  - Haaf, Gunter - 1975 - Germany - Journalism, 1974-1986 (Box 84, Folder 683)
  - Haaf, Gunter - 1975 - Germany - Journalism, 1974-1986 (Box 84, Folder 684)
  - Haack, Susan - 1975 - England - Philosophy, 1975-1990 (Box 84, Folder 685)
  - Haddock, John Robert - 1970 - England - Business Administration, 1970-1988 (Box 84, Folder 686)